Oh, yeah, that's Captain Sweatpants.
(Leonard:)He doesn't really help the point
I'm trying to make.
- Got it, got it, got it.
(Sheldon:)- Need it.
- Need it.
- Let it go, Sheldon.
- Why should I let it go? I saw it first.
- Yes, but I saw it from the front.
- A far less impressive feat.
Oh, come on, I need this
for my Batman collection.
- I need it for my Robin collection.
- Rock Paper Scissors Lizard Spock?
(Sheldon:)Why would I gamble? It's mine. Let go.
- You let go.
- No, you.
- Problem?
- Yes. He won't let go of my comic book.
- It's my comic book.
- Leonard, we need a ruling.
(Leonard:)Uh, cut it in half?
- Excuse me.
- Oh, hello again.
(Penny:)Hi. What would you recommend
as a present for a 13-year-old boy?
(Stuart:)A 13-year-old girl.